<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="http://localhost:4000/cf/feed.xslt.xml"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.4.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/cf/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/cf/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-01-08T14:19:36-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/cf//</id><title type="html">Your awesome title</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Blue Diamond Growers Plant Receives Excellence in Safety Award</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/cf/blue-diamond-growers-safety-award/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Blue Diamond Growers Plant Receives Excellence in Safety Award" /><published>2017-11-01T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-11-01T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/cf/blue-diamond-growers-safety-award</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/cf/blue-diamond-growers-safety-award/">&lt;p&gt;Lehigh congratulates its account Blue Diamond Growers on their recent Million Work Hours Award from the National Safety Council. The award recognizes the Blue Diamond Salida manufacturing plant in California for achieving 2 million consecutive work hours without an occupational injury or illness resulting in days away from work from June 2015 to September 2017. The plant employs 558 workers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blue Diamond President and CEO Mark Jenson said, “Ensuring the safety of our more than 1,500 employees is the highest priority in all Blue Diamond’s operations. Less than half a percent of manufacturing facilities this size have achieved this milestone.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the leader in managed safety footwear programs, a vital part of decreasing workplace lost-time injuries, we share our account’s dedication and drive to a zero harm culture and support them in their continued pursuit of safety excellence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;![Congrats! Blue Diamond Growers For 2 Million Hours with no lost-time injuries][http://info.rockybrands.com/rs/018-APH-439/images/cf-email-171128-zeroinjuries.jpg]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Lehigh CustomFit Territory Sales Manager, Caleb Robinson, had the pleasure of celebrating the excellence in safety award with his account, Blue Diamond.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">Lehigh congratulates its account Blue Diamond Growers on their recent Million Work Hours Award from the National Safety Council. The award recognizes the Blue Diamond Salida manufacturing plant in California for achieving 2 million consecutive work hours without an occupational injury or illness resulting in days away from work from June 2015 to September 2017. The plant employs 558 workers.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://info.rockybrands.com/rs/018-APH-439/images/cf-email-171128-zeroinjuries.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Lehigh Announces New District Sales Manager - BRENT BECKER</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/cf/new-district-sales-manager/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lehigh Announces New District Sales Manager - BRENT BECKER" /><published>2017-06-01T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-06-01T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/cf/new-district-sales-manager</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/cf/new-district-sales-manager/">&lt;p&gt;Lehigh is pleased to introduce Brent Becker as our newest Territory Sales Manager covering the New England states of Vermont, Maine, New Hampshire, Massachusetts, Rhode Island and Connecticut, as well as New York City.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brent will be responsible for taking care of existing Lehigh customers in this territory as well as working to secure new ones. He joins the existing internal team of Business Development Representative James Spratlin and Account Sales Representative Rick Sheets who will all work together as an undoubtedly strong team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brent is a graduate of Bloomsburg University in Bloomsburg, PA with a Bachelor’s Degree in Political Science. Prior to joining Lehigh, Brent worked as a Contractor Sales Representative for 84 Lumber.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have questions? Want to introduce yourself? Feel free to reach out and welcome Brent as your new area representative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Email: &lt;strong&gt;brent.becker@lehighoutfitters.com&lt;/strong&gt;
Office: &lt;strong&gt;800-444-4086 ext. 2589&lt;/strong&gt;
Cell: &lt;strong&gt;847-922-9398&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">Lehigh is pleased to introduce Brent Becker as our newest Territory Sales Manager covering the New England states of Vermont, Maine, New Hampshire, Massachusetts, Rhode Island and Connecticut, as well as New York City.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://d1jdomzv2hp689.cloudfront.net/content/data/18_810.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Lehigh Launches New QuickFit Collection</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/cf/quickfit/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lehigh Launches New QuickFit Collection" /><published>2017-04-01T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-04-01T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/cf/quickfit</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/cf/quickfit/">&lt;p&gt;Lehigh Outfitters, a nationwide online retailer of work footwear for corporations, employees and individual consumers, has launched its new QuickFit collection encompassing free overnight delivery on two protective toe footwear styles for only $89.00 per pair*.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The QuickFit collection is another step forward in Lehigh’s continuing effort to fill the gaps in our customer’s programs to procure durable and dependable footwear for their employees,” said Sarah Milligan, Vice President of Sales and Operations for Lehigh Outfitters. “Our CustomFit kiosks that launched in 2013 were a revolutionary approach to supplying workplace footwear. We had analyzed the current environment of how most companies were buying their safety shoes with the mission of improving efficiency, selection and savings. Now we’ve advanced that custom service even more by making these styles available for immediate delivery. This Lehigh exclusive collection makes it easier than ever for our customers to quickly acquire affordable boots to fit new hires or replacements.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;QuickFit style LEHI009 is ideal for most heavy industrial applications. The six-inch waterproof boots also feature 100 grams of 3M™ Thinsulate™ insulation and electrical hazard protection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;QuickFit style LEHI015 is an exceptional general-use boot. Made from real leather, the six-inch boot features electrical hazard protection along with a removable polyurethane footbed and PVC outsole for shock absorbtion and all-day comfort and support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shipping on any QuickFit order is free and FedEx next business day delivery is guaranteed on any order placed before 1 p.m. EST. (where service is applicable). $89.00 per pair is available on CustomFit Corporate Shoe Program sites only.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.customfit.me/quickfit&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE&lt;/a&gt; To learn more about the Lehigh QuickFit collection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lehigh Outfitters is one of the largest providers and manufacturers of safety footwear in the industry selling both direct to the consumer and to businesses offering safety shoe programs. Owned and operated by Rocky Brands, Inc., out of Nelsonville, OH, the company was founded on the hard-working ingenuity of the Pennsylvania Lehigh Valley.&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">Lehigh Outfitters, a nationwide online retailer of work footwear for corporations, employees and individual consumers, has launched its new QuickFit collection encompassing free overnight delivery on two protective toe footwear styles for only $89.00 per pair*.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://d1jdomzv2hp689.cloudfront.net/content/data/18_806.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">3rd Annual Steel Safety Day</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/cf/3rd-annual-steel-safety-day/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="3rd Annual Steel Safety Day" /><published>2017-04-01T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-04-01T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/cf/3rd-annual-steel-safety-day</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/cf/3rd-annual-steel-safety-day/">&lt;p&gt;One of Lehigh’s core values is safety and we support any initiative that shares and promotes that value to the customers we serve. The 3rd annual Steel Safety Day on April 28th, established by the World Steel Association (WSA), reinforces creating and maintaining a safer work environment across the entire steel industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At inception, the WSA defined the 5 most common major causes of workplace safety incidents to focus on - moving machinery, falling from heights, falling items, gas and asphyxiation, and moving cranes. Each year one of the causes is highlighted with knowledge and information for prevention. This year focuses on Staying Safe While Working At Height. Check out this detailed graphic the WSA put together to help better understand the safety practices to reduce risk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In addition:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The above practices are excellent points in helping to prevent an occurance or hazard. Lehigh also highly recommends always enforcing a safety footwear policy and requirement for steady footing when working from any height or on a ladder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the steel industry our most commonly purchased footwear is MetGuards. This type of boot incorporates an extra piece of durable material that lays on top of the boot to protect the metatarsal bones of the foot from heavy impact. Lehigh carries a wide variety of styles in both internal and external options. If you have a CustomFit account check them out here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For employees who spend any time working at height on a ladder, the right boot makes all the difference. The best boot to have is a debris-releasing, anti-slip outsole with a right-angled heel for proper rung gripping. Check out our more in-depth article about Boots and Ladders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you do not already receive the benefits and savings of a CustomFit account Contact Us Today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information on Steel Safety Day visit WorldSteel.org.&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">One of Lehigh’s core values is safety and we support any initiative that shares and promotes that value to the customers we serve. The 3rd annual Steel Safety Day on April 28th, established by the World Steel Association (WSA), reinforces creating and maintaining a safer work environment across the entire steel industry.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://d1jdomzv2hp689.cloudfront.net/content/data/18_807.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Lehigh Announces New District Sales Manager - GREG FROST</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/cf/new-district-sales-manager-greg-frost/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lehigh Announces New District Sales Manager - GREG FROST" /><published>2015-12-01T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2015-12-01T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/cf/new-district-sales-manager-greg-frost</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/cf/new-district-sales-manager-greg-frost/">&lt;p&gt;Lehigh is proud to introduce our newest Lehigh District Sales Manager covering the Greater Chicago and Milwaukee area, Greg Frost. Promoted from an Inside Sales Representative, Greg has demonstrated leadership, innitiative, and dedication. “We are thrilled to have Greg move into the Chicago and Milwaukee area and have no doubt he will be effective in strengthening our existing partnerships while reaching out and creating new ones,” said Jim Murphy, regional vice president of sales.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Greg has been with Lehigh Outfitters since June of 2014. Prior to working with Lehigh, he worked in sales for Sherwin Williams for 3 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have questions? Want to introduce yourself? Feel free to reach out and welcome Greg as your new area representative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Email: &lt;strong&gt;GregFrost@LehighOutfitters.com&lt;/strong&gt;
Phone: &lt;strong&gt;800-444-4086 Ext. 2116&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.customfit.me/newsandevents/&quot;&gt;See all News &amp;amp; Events&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">Lehigh is proud to introduce our newest Lehigh District Sales Manager covering the Greater Chicago and Milwaukee area, Greg Frost. Promoted from an Inside Sales Representative, Greg has demonstrated leadership, innitiative, and dedication. “We are thrilled to have Greg move into the Chicago and Milwaukee area and have no doubt he will be effective in strengthening our existing partnerships while reaching out and creating new ones,” said Jim Murphy, regional vice president of sales.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://d1jdomzv2hp689.cloudfront.net/content/data/18_804.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Top 3 Reasons To See Us At The 2015 NSC CONGRESS AND EXPO</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/cf/top-3-reasons-to-see-us-at-2015-nsc-congress-and-expo/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Top 3 Reasons To See Us At The 2015 NSC CONGRESS AND EXPO" /><published>2015-09-01T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2015-09-01T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/cf/top-3-reasons-to-see-us-at-2015-nsc-congress-and-expo</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/cf/top-3-reasons-to-see-us-at-2015-nsc-congress-and-expo/">&lt;p&gt;The 2015 National Safety Council Congress and Expo kicks off tomorrow. For safety, health and environmental professionals, it’s a must-attend event for revolutionary technologies, education, networking and finding the newest products and services needed to stay competitive. Lehigh Outfitters has been a proud vendor for many years demonstrating the value of our service-driven, cost-saving and industry-leading solution to a better Safety Footwear Program. While there are many reasons to stop by our Booth 3066, here are the Top 3. We hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://info.rockybrands.com/rs/018-APH-439/images/NSC-2015-Invite_09.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The top 3 reasons to see us at NSC 2015: Savings, win a prize, and see our smiling faces&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">The 2015 National Safety Council Congress and Expo kicks off tomorrow. For safety, health and environmental professionals, it’s a must-attend event for revolutionary technologies, education, networking and finding the newest products and services needed to stay competitive. Lehigh Outfitters has been a proud vendor for many years demonstrating the value of our service-driven, cost-saving and industry-leading solution to a better Safety Footwear Program. While there are many reasons to stop by our Booth 3066, here are the Top 3. We hope to see you there!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://d1jdomzv2hp689.cloudfront.net/content/data/18_803.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Safety Hazard Alert!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/cf/safety-hazard-alert/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Safety Hazard Alert!" /><published>2015-08-01T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2015-08-01T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/cf/safety-hazard-alert</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/cf/safety-hazard-alert/">&lt;p&gt;The Washington State Department of Labor and Industries has issued a Safety Hazard Alert to anyone who uses products containing hydrofluoric (HF) acid, especially those who work in commercial car washes and auto detail as car and truck washes and rust removers and brighteners are likely to contain it. In Washington alone, one worker has died and 48 have been burned after exposure to car and truck wash.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Protection is highly important! You should stop using all products that contain HF if possible. Researchers found that “Products containing both diluted-use concentrations of less than 1 percent HF and concentrated formulations of up to 20 percent HF are dangerous to workers.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These incidents and cases stress the necessity of always wearing proper PPE such as gloves, face shields and boots, when working with solvents and chemicals as you never know what may be dangerous or harmful to you. Our selection of rubber boots is superior to most – log into your CustomFit site and check them out. If you need to protect and provide for your workers but don’t have a safety shoe program, we are confident you’ll find the quality safety boots and service you need with us – &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.customfit.me/customfit&quot;&gt;Get CustomFit Today&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">The Washington State Department of Labor and Industries has issued a Safety Hazard Alert to anyone who uses products containing hydrofluoric (HF) acid, especially those who work in commercial car washes and auto detail as car and truck washes and rust removers and brighteners are likely to contain it. In Washington alone, one worker has died and 48 have been burned after exposure to car and truck wash.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://d1jdomzv2hp689.cloudfront.net/content/data/18_800.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">June is National Safety Month</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/cf/june-is-national-safety-month/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="June is National Safety Month" /><published>2015-06-01T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2015-06-01T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/cf/june-is-national-safety-month</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/cf/june-is-national-safety-month/">&lt;p&gt;June is National Safety Month. Observed annually, the National Safety Council (NSC) uses the month to focus on, promote and communicate ways of reducing the leading causes of injury and death in the workplace, at home and in the community. This year’s theme, “What I Have To Live For” encourages individuals to think about safety prevention as a way to celebrate and realize their passions. Materials, webinars and other tools are available for supervisors and managers to promote and instill better daily awareness, habits and procedures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an industry leader in safety footwear, Lehigh CustomFit is a proud supporter of all ways that help you stay safe on the job and everywhere you go and live. Like NSC, our overall mission is safety. As we strive to continually provide you with up-to-date and relevant resources and articles, we encourage you to keep checking back with us here at customfit.me. If you are not receiving our awesome informational and promotional emails, sign up today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OSHA qualifies footwear protection as an essential PPE (personal performance equipment) and we value our responsibility in providing you and your employees with a quality pair of boots that you trust to keep you safe. In doing that, we also believe you appreciate the hows and whys of safety so we also strive to provide information to help you better understand the best ways you can be safe and instill safety. After all, as we say on our About Us page, “Providing quality safety footwear with exceptional service and value is what we do,” and we hope that you put your trust in us to do that for YOU. Contact us today to improve your safety footwear program, and thus; the safety of you and your workers.&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">June is National Safety Month. Observed annually, the National Safety Council (NSC) uses the month to focus on, promote and communicate ways of reducing the leading causes of injury and death in the workplace, at home and in the community. This year’s theme, “What I Have To Live For” encourages individuals to think about safety prevention as a way to celebrate and realize their passions. Materials, webinars and other tools are available for supervisors and managers to promote and instill better daily awareness, habits and procedures.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://d1jdomzv2hp689.cloudfront.net/content/data/18_795.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Safety Week 2015</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/cf/safety-week-2015/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Safety Week 2015" /><published>2015-05-01T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2015-05-01T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/cf/safety-week-2015</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/cf/safety-week-2015/">&lt;p&gt;Across the US, more then 80,000 construction workers suffer an injury on the job site every year. That’s incredible; and it’s obviously way too many. So, the over 40 national and global construction firms making up CISI (the Construction Industry Safety Initiative) and IIF (the Incident and Injury-Free Executive Forum) have come together for the 2nd Annual US Industry Safety Week May 3rd through the 9th.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Construction firms of all sizes across the country are encouraged to work together to eliminate worker injury. SafetyWeek2015.com states the collective mission of the campaign is to partner together in:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Thanking workers for supporting safety and recognizing their efforts to be injury free&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Increasing awareness of the importance of being committed to safety, every day&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Inspiring all of us to share best practices and to work together to strengthen our industry’s safety culture&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Celebrating the need to be injury free&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Conducting on-site safety awareness activities to support education&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Companies, Safety Directors, Foremen, Shift Supervisors and Human Resources need to take this opportunity to recommit and focus-in on reducing jobsite injuries. If not this week, designate another specific week for your workers to demonstrate your commitment to the value of their lives and the work they do. Pledge to make a difference and to be a leader in safety.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lehigh CustomFit makes that pledge to you. As a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.customfit.me/whoweare&quot;&gt;leader in the Safety Footwear Industry&lt;/a&gt; we are dedicated to providing an expansive quality selection to meet your every need. From steel and composite toe to metatarsal and puncture-resistant our products have features that provide protection from environmental elements as well as superior comfort for all-day jobs on your feet to help prevent fatigue that can lead to poor decisions. Our &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.customfit.me/customfit/default.aspx&quot;&gt;Safety Footwear programs&lt;/a&gt; facilitate service options that help increase the percentage of your workers wearing their safety shoes and thus eliminating injury.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Click to visit the official site of and for more information on &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.safetyweek2015.com/&quot;&gt;Safety Week 2015&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">Across the US, more then 80,000 construction workers suffer an injury on the job site every year. That’s incredible; and it’s obviously way too many. So, the over 40 national and global construction firms making up CISI (the Construction Industry Safety Initiative) and IIF (the Incident and Injury-Free Executive Forum) have come together for the 2nd Annual US Industry Safety Week May 3rd through the 9th.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://d1jdomzv2hp689.cloudfront.net/content/data/18_786.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Lehigh Announces New District Sales Manager - MICHAEL JACOBS</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/cf/new-district-sales-manager-michael-jacobs/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lehigh Announces New District Sales Manager - MICHAEL JACOBS" /><published>2015-05-01T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2015-05-01T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/cf/new-district-sales-manager-michael-jacobs</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/cf/new-district-sales-manager-michael-jacobs/">&lt;p&gt;Lehigh is proud to introduce our newest Lehigh District Sales Manager covering the states of Texas, Oklahoma and Louisiana, Michael Jacobs. We are very excited to have Mike on board - his vast knowledge of the industry will undoubtedly benefit our customers,” said Jim Murphy, regional vice president of sales.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Michael is a veteran of the footwear industry with 17 years of working for companies such as Wolverine Worldwide and Nike. In addition, Michael has 6 years experience in the Home Furnishings industry. He holds a Bachelor’s Degree from the University of Chattanooga, TN.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have questions? Want to introduce yourself? Feel free to reach out and welcome Michael as your new area representative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Email: Michael.Jacobs@LehighOutfitters.com
Phone: 800-444-4086&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.customfit.me/newsandevents/&quot;&gt;See all News &amp;amp; Events&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">Lehigh is proud to introduce our newest Lehigh District Sales Manager covering the states of Texas, Oklahoma and Louisiana, Michael Jacobs. We are very excited to have Mike on board - his vast knowledge of the industry will undoubtedly benefit our customers,” said Jim Murphy, regional vice president of sales.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://d1jdomzv2hp689.cloudfront.net/content/data/18_787.png" /></entry></feed>
